A Guide to the Papers of the Cook Family 1872-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- Financial Documents
  - Documents and Receipts
    - Allen M. Cook - Virginia Beach and Norfolk Taxpayer's Receipts 1933-1941 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Allen M. Cook - Notes (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Emma Blow Freeman Cook 1915-1956, 2 folders (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 37-38)
    - Henry Clarico Freeman Cook (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Pepita B. Cook January-July 1976 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 40)
- Photographs
  - Cook Family
    - Edgewater Home (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Arthur Clarico Freeman II
    - Elsa and Child 1915 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 2)
    - World War II Searchlights October 1941-September 1942 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Katherine Groner Shropshire 1941 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Katherine Groner Shropshire (negative) August 1941 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Emma Blow Freeman
    - Miscellaneous 1918-1919 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Allen Merriam Cook
    - Miscellaneous 1876, 1896 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (not dated) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Elfrieda Blow Freeman Tice
    - Miscellaneous (not dated) (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Tice (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Merton B. Tice
    - Campaign Photograph (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 11)
    - VFW, Judge, Military 1945-1955 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Allen Blow Cook
    - Military (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Childhood Photographs (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Henry Clarico Freeman Cook
    - Clarice 1910 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Twins - Freeman and Clarice 1909-1913 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Freeman 1914-1926 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Freeman 1931-1948 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Freeman - Naval Service (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Blue Ridge Sanitarium 1928 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous People
    - Navy (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Sailors on a Naval Vessel (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous and Unknown People, 7 folders (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 24-30)
    - Unknown Profile (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Places
    - Navy - Postcards (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Navy (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Panama (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Victoria, British Columbia (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous and Unknown (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Negatives
    - Miscellaneous and Unknown (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 37)
- Literary Productions
  - Allen M. Cook, Naval Reports
    - Investigation at St. Juliens Creek July 1911 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 38)
    - St. Juliens Creek Magazine (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Torpedo Boats in Reserve January 19, 1903 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 40)
    - St. Juliens Creek - Manpower in an emergency; Labor Output (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Accounting and Cost Keeping (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Records of Previous Costs and Determining Indirect Charges (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 43)
    - "Economy in the Navy...", 3 folders (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 44-46)
    - "Organization - The Organization of a Navy Yard..." (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 47)
    - List of Job Orders, St. Juliens Creek Magazine September 30, 1910 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 48)
    - "Instructions Relative to Cost of Work for Industrial Navy Yards" (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Standard for Making 5"50 Charges April 21, 1911 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Standard of Cost and Details of Making 12" Bags June, 1910 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Expenditure Reports, St. Juliens Creek (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Administration of Naval Industrial Establishments (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Report on the Fitness of Officers October 12, 1896 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Assorted
    - Arthur Clarico Freeman II, invention (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Allen M. Cook, Princess Anne & Norfolk Mutual B & L Association August 1933-December 1936 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Edgewater Garden Club 1938 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 57)
    - History - The Camm Family; Littleton, Walker and Tazewell (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Arthur C. Freeman, Memoirs 1939 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Essays (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Portion of Essay re: Humanity (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Poetry (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Story Plot about Marriage and Infidelity (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Recipes (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Reminiscences, Arthur C. Freeman II June 1944 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Reminiscences, the Arrest of Lizzie Freeman May 1922 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Research Notes (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Speeches (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, A-M (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, N-Z (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 70)
- Legal Documents
  - Business Documents, Allen Merriam Cook
    - Agreements September 1913-July 1940 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Certificate of Incorporation, Princess Anne and Norfolk Mutual and Loan Association May 1921 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Contracts, Ferndale Corp., A-F July 1911-July 1925 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Contracts, Ferndale Corp., G-M July 1911-July 1925 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Contracts, Ferndale Corp., S-Z July 1911-July 1925 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Contracts, Princess Anne and Norfolk Land Company January 1921-November 1940 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Contracts, Miscellaneous June 1916-December 1940 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Contracts, Blank (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Deeds October 1905-January 1941 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Proxies July 1922 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Merger Agreement - Mutual Federal Savings and Loan Association, and First Federal Savings and Loan (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Deed Release, Princess Anne & Norfolk Land Company to Edwin J. Smith and S.Q. Collins Jr. (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Directors, Norfolk Federal Savings and Loan Association, continuation of service (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Formation of corporation to buy and handle lots at Glen Park (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous 1918-1940 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Legal Documents, Blank (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Personal Documents, Cook Family
    - Revocable Change of Beneficiary, Allen Merriam Cook September 1940 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Insurance Policies, Allen Merriam and Emma Freeman Cook August 1953-June 1955 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Contract, Hampton Roads Vermin Exterminating July 1935 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Deeds, Emma Freeman Cook August 1909-March 1929 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Endorsement, Emma Freeman Cook May 1952 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Demand, Emma Freeman Cook and Family (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Birth Certificate, Henry Clarico Freeman Cook March 1909 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Documento Privado, Henry Clarico Freeman Cook November 1970 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Sale (in Spanish), Henry Clarico Freeman Cook August 1976 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Power of Attorney, Henry Clarico Freeman and Pepita Cook November 1950 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Share Certificate, Atlantic Engineering & Construction Corp. January 1907 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Appraisal of Estate, J.A. Campbell Groner February 1951 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 99)
- Scrapbooks and Scrapbook material
  - Allen Merriam Cook 1896-1898 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Allen Merriam Cook 1897-1900 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
- Artifacts
  - Allen Merriam Cook, Foreign Legion Cap 1941 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Henry Clarico Freeman Cook, Picture of Sailboat (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
  - International Code Flag Cards (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Key (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Picture with the Initials "G.B." (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
- Charts, Lists, Diagrams, Real Estate Plats, Maps
  - Planting Charts and Tables 1943 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Itinerary for Elfrieda Tice (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
  - List of Letter File Title Sheet (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pilot Chart of the North Atlantic Ocean April 1916 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sketch of Farm, Afton, Virginia (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Labor Chart for St. Juliens Naval Magazine January 1909-February 1911 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Sketch of Freeman Night Flag January 1952 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Sketch of Sailboat, "Water Gipsy" (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Typical Floor Plan Proposed Apartment Building, Arthur C. Freeman II (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Handwritten Map of Property near Carrsville, Virginia (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Sketch of Edmund Bradford Estate (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Assorted Sketches of Property (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Sketch of Real Estate Plat, Stratford Court (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Assorted Sketches of Real Estate Plats (I) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Assorted Sketches of Real Estate Plats (II) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Allen Merriam Cook, Telephone List, Brotherhood of St. Andrews (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Bill of Materials for Farm House (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 24)
  - List of "Native Trees, Shrubs, and Vines That Are Adaptable toYards In Certain Areas (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 25)
  - List of Manufacturing Plants-Norfolk (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Deeds from Ferndale Corp. (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Real Estate Lists, Coleman Place (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Real Estate Lists, East Coleman Place (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Real Estate Lists, Fox Hall Place (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate Lists, Fox Hall Residence Park (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Real Estate Lists, Osburne Lots (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Real Estate Lists, Rosemont Gardens (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Real Estate Lists, Miscellaneous I (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Real Estate Lists, Miscellaneous II (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Real Estate Lists, Plat of Property of Bay View Beach Corporation 1920 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Plat Showing Proposed Extensio of Ballentine Blvd. Jan.1925 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Map of Beachway(Rosemont)Princess Anne County May 1922 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Map of Belmont Place, Norfolk County Jan. 1920 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Map of Property of Broad Creek Land Corporation Dec.1906 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Plat of the S.W. Brooks Farm on Lynnhaven River, Princess Anne County Dec.1920 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Platt of Property of I.H. Buchanan, Princess Anne County June 1908 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Plan of E.U. Buell's Land-Southern Branch of Elizabeth River April 1905 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Amended Plat of Campostella Heights May 1920 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Cape Henry (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Chesterfield Heights-Section I,Aug. 1917 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Plat of John Daly Farm, Princess Anne County Feb.1918 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Plat of W.Davis's Farmon Broad Bay, The Palisades Property of Bay View Farm-Princess Anne County Nov.1925 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Map of East Norfolk, Princess Anne County (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Plan of Edgewater (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Plat Showing Edgewater Annex A, Suburb of Norfolk on the Elizabeth River June 1901 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Plat Showing Subdivision No.2 of Elmhurst-Norfolk County I March 1922 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Plat Showing Subdivision No.2 of Elmhurst-Norfolk County II March 1922 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Property of Farmer's Manufacturing Co.-Situated in Lindenwood, Norfolk (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Map showing Proposed Layout of Federal and Municipal Buildings Aug.1929 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Garden City, Lynnhaven District, Princess Anne County March 1923 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Glenrock, Property of Ferndale Corp.-Eastern Branch Elizabeth 1916 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Property of Princess Anne and Norfolk Land Co.-Eastern Branch Elizabeth River 1907 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Plat of Gowrie Park-Norfolk July 1923 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Plat showing Proposed Extension of Grace St. and Adjacent Properties Nov. 1916 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Plat of Greenwich Terrace near Greenwich, Princess Anne County May 1924 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Plat Showing Subdivision of Jefferson D.Guy's Farm, Norfolk Co. April 1922 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Plat of the Hardy Family Berkley (Norfolk) March 1902 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Section "B" Hollywood on Norfolk-Virginia Beach Blvd. Oct.1924 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Pleasure House Camp Feb. 1924 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Plat of Lands Owned by Indian River Park & Improvement Co.-Norfolk and Princess Anne Cos Nov. 1916 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Map of Ingleside, Norfolk County Nov.1911 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Kenilworth-Property of Kenilworth Realty Corp. (n.d.) (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Lafayette Terrace-Norfolk I March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Lafayette Terrace-Norfolk II March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lakeview Heights Nov. 1921 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Plat 2A-C of Lakewood-Norfolk Aug. 1925, March 1926 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Property of A.J. Makinson-Princess Anne Co. (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Map of Milburn Manor on Norfolk-VB Blvd-Princess Anne Co. April, 1930 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Map of Morgan Farm on Southern Branch of Elizabeth River April 1891 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Property of Morningside Realty Corp.-Norfolk Co. Aug. 1919 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Plate 2 City of Norfolk (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Plane 7 City of Norfolk March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Plats of Norfolk Highlands (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Map of Plots Nos. 14 & 15-Oceana Gardens June 20, 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Oceana Terrace-Princess Anne Co. (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Plat No.2-Overbrook Realty Corp. Nov. 1919 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Plan of Lots Situated in Princess Anne Co. Surveyed for B.F. Owens-Corner of VB Blvd and Great Neck Rd. March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Plat of Properties of O.B. McLeaon-Park Ave. and Princess Anne Rd. Norfolk (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Oceana Eastern Bridge Rd, London Bridge Rd. March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Plan of Property Situated in Princess Anne Co. Surveyed for Frank P. Stras Jan. 1924 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Plan of Property Situated in Princess Anne Co. Surveyed for H. L. Bullis Nov. 1922 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Property of H.G. Robinson on Lafayette River Between Bowdens Ferry Rd. and Colley AVe.-Norfolk March 1923 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Maps of "Small Farms"- Princess Anne Co.- Norfolk Rolleston Corp. March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Plat of Rosemont being that Part of Jacksondale Owned by the Rosemont Corp. March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Blvd Road Map-Rosemont March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Map of Part of East Norfolk in Princess Anne Co. March 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Rosemont Gardens-Princess Anne Co. (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Rosemont Park-A Suburb Near Norfolk I Nov. 1924 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Rosemont Park-A Suburb Near Norfolk II Nov. 1924 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Rosemont Park-A Suburb Near Norfolk III Nov. 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Sea Breeze-Addition to Virginia Beach Princess Anne Co. March 1926 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Map of O.F. Smith's Property, Norfolk Aug. 1916 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Plat of a Part of Summerville, Princess Anne Co. Nov. 1920 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Sunset Park Opposite State Rifle Range Virginia Beach July 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Division of C.C. Iption Farm near Oak Grove-Norfolk Co. March 1932 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Map of Industrial Property of West Ghent Annex Corp (n.d.) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Plat of Whitehead Subdivision, Property of C.T. Whitehead-Princess Anne Co. July 1928 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Olney Rd.-Redgate Ave. Area-Norfolk (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Plan of Showing Location of Proposed Apartment Building (Greenway Ct.-Redgate Ave.),(n.d.) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Plat of S.N. Woodward's Land on Broad Creek, Princess Anne Co. Feb. 1921 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Ballentine Place-Suburb of Norfolk Aug. 1910 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Map of Bird Neck Pt. Club Section-Princess Anne Co Feb.1921 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Edgewater-Property of New Edgewater Corp. Nov. 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Map of Easton Place-Suburb of Norfolk Dec. 1911 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 44)
  - East Fairmont-Suburb of Norfolk Nov. 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Euclid Place-Suburb of Norfolk March 1906 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Map of Ingleside-Suburb Beautiful(Property of Barton Myers) Nov. 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Ocean View Annex Co.-Norfolk (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Advertisements for Sale of Lots in Oceana Gardens (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Piece of Map Including Pennsylvania Avenue (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Map of Lafayette Residence Park (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Copy of Part of Plat of of Old Tiberius Lambert Property (New edgewater) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Amended Plat of Larchmont-Property of Larchmont Realty Corp June 1909 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Survey of Lots 17 & 18-Block 45 The Ghent Co.- The Norfolk Co. For Emma F. Cook et al. May 1950 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Proposed Amusement Bldg. Rosemont Park (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Plat of Ocean Park Property of Ocean Park Corp,Norfolk April, 1912 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Topographic Map-Cape Henry Quadrangle 1919 ed. (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Map of the Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line R.R. and Connections 1919 I (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Map of the Norfolk and Portsmouth Belt Line R.R. and Connections II 1919 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Map of Harbor Lines, Tanners Creek, Virginia 1910 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Proposed Change in Harbor Lines (Sheet No.5 Sewall Pt. Section) Elizabeth River 1910 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 61)
  - High Tide Downtown Norfolk Aug. 1933 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Map of Norfolk Business District (Published by Henry Eagleton) Nov. 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Official Map of Norfolk and Vicinity (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Architectural Plans for a Farm House (U.S. Dept of Agriculture) Nov. 1925 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Architectural Plans for a Two Story House (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Craigmillar-Afton, Virginia (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Arlington National Cemetary April,1939 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Map of a Portion of Jamestown, Rhode Island, Folder Map of Alaska 1936ed., 1909 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Nostrand's Map of New York (n.d.) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Map of the City of Philadelphia (Arthur Clarico Freeman II) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Map of Alaska 1936 ed. (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Topographic Maps-Kansas, Missouri, Colorado, and New Mexico, Texas 1917-1921 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Keyon's Map of the Western Battle Front of Europe 1918 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Cram's Pictographic Map of the Pacific Area (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Cram's Panoramic Map of the World (n.d.) (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Piece of Unidentified Map (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Unidentified Map (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 78)
- Series XII: Genealogy
  - Correspondence re. Genealogy of Cook Family 1898 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence re. Genealogy of Cook Family 1902 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence re. Genealogy of Cook Family 1903 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence re. Genealogy of Cook Family 1904 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cook Family News Jan.1904 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Blank Genealogical Research Data Forms (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Genealogical Research for Cook Family History I (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Genealogical Research for Cook Family History II 1898 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Genealogical Research for Cook Family History III (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Genealogical Research for Cook Family History 5th Generation (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Genealogical Research for Cook Family History 6th Generation (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Genealogical Research for Cook Family History (Misc.) (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Notebook Cook Family History I (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Notebook Cook Family History II (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Notebook-Record of Cook Family Genealogy (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 15)